Guide to the Rev. William A. Lawson papers, 1955-2008 MS 532
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Taped Recordings of Sermons (audiocassettes, one per sermon), 1996-2004
  - October 12, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 26, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 2, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 9, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 16, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 23, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 7, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 21, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 28, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 4, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 11, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 15, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 25, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 7, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 28, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 4, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 11, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 18, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 2, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 13, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 27, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 4, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 11, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 18, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 25, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 8, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 15, 2004: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 14, 2004: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
- Series IV: Wheeler Avenue Baptist Church publications, 1962-2003
  General note
  Note: Missing Binder: July-December, 1996, should be between WABC Bulletins: April-June, 1996 and WABC Bulletins: January-June, 1997
  - WABC Anniversary Booklets, 1962-1968. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - WABC Anniversary Booklets, 1969-1975. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - WABC Anniversary Booklets, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3-)
  - WABC Anniversary Booklets, 1988-2000. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - WABC Anniversary Booklets, 1988-2000. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - WABC Women's Day, 1976. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - WABC Pictorial Directory, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - WABC Pictorial Directory, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - WABC Publication "The Scroll"; April-May, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 1994. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 1995. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 1995. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 1995. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 1995. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 1996. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-June, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-December, 1997. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-June, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-December, 1998. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-June, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 1999. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 1999. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - unspecified (Box 7)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - WABC Bulletins:April-June, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 2000. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 2000. (Box 7, Folder -)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - WABC Bulletins:July-September, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-September, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - WABC Bulletins: October-December, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - WABC Bulletins: January-March, 2003. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - WABC Bulletins: April-June, 2003. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - WABC Bulletins: July-December, 2003. (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Series V: Personal Materials, 1977-2008
  - Houston Newspages: "The Triumph of 'Wild Bill Lawson'". (Box 7, Folder -16)
  - Newspaper clippings and photocopies. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - National Coalition of 100 Black Women-Luncheon 1994. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - William A. Lawson 80th Birthday Celebration. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Testimonial Dinner honoring W.A.L.. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Compositions of Appreciation presented to W.A.L.. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - A Short History of the Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Letter of Appreciation from President Jimmy Carter. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Personal Ephemera. (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Series VI: Photographs
  This collection of photographs spans much of Bill Lawson's adult life and covers many church, civic, and community events of which Lawson was a part. Civil rights protests, the construction of the WABC Sanctuary, and travel to the Holy Land are just a few of the topics well-documented by the photographs.
  - Letter of Appreciation from President Jimmy Carter. (Box 8, Folder -)
  - Family photos, including wedding of Rev. Bill and Mrs. Audrey Lawson, 50 year Sumner High School reunion, and trip to Holy Land; photos of Wheeler Ave. Baptist Church, including building renovations and services such as weddings, baptisms, fellowships, and boy and girl scouts; SCLC Civil Rights Protests; recognition for Civil Rights efforts; and Houston's Millenium Makers book featuring Rev. Bill and Mrs. Audrey Lawson, 1970-2000 (Box 8)